"I am quite serious. Look at those kids.
The boys want to get the girls into bed so
they can have their corks popped off their
bottles and forth. When a man blows his nose
you dont call it love. Why get all misty-eyed 
when a man blows another part of his anatomy?
As for the girls, they're either going along for
the ride because they can get the things they 
want from the boys, or else maybe they enjoy 
being in bed too. Thought I doubt it.
I never knew an eighteen-year-old boy who
didnt drop the egg off his spoon at the first fence."

"But thats list! Youre talking about lust, not love."
